

HASSAM SALEEM

Full Stack Developer

RESUME OBJECTIVE

Software Developer with 3+ years of experience in Web and Desktop App Development. I have strong hand on different types of systems (listed in Projects Section). I seek a full-time position in the related field of Software world, where I can apply and enhance my knowledge and skills for continuous improvement.

EXPERIENCE

DOT NET/PHP DEVELOPER

GrizzlyAtoms LLC | Mar 2020 - Oct 2020

 Working at GrizzlyAtoms LLC (U.S.A based company) as a Web App Developer and Scraping Incharge.

DOT NET/PHP DEVELOPER

SofticEra Faisalabad | Aug 2019 - Mar 2020

 Worked at SofticEra as a Web/Desktop App Developer for 7-months duration.

WEB & DESKTOP APP DEVELOPER

Zee Solution Faisalabad | Sept 2018 - Aug 2019

 Worked at Zee Solution as a Web/Desktop App Developer for 11-months duration.

WEB CONTENT & ARTICLE WRITER

Axiom Solution Faisalabad | Feb 2018 - Aug 2018

• Worked as Web content & Article writer at Axiom Solution for 6-months duration.

WEB & DESKTOP APP DEVELOPER

UNIAL Solution Faisalabad | Sept 2017 - Dec 2017

 Worked as internee at UNIAL Solution for Web & Desktop App Development for 3-months duration.

PROJECTS

- POS System
- Stock Management
- Inventory Management
- E-Commerce Websites
- CMS Systems
- Blockchain System
- Invoicing System
- Booking System

EDUCATION

BS(HONS) IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

GC University, Faisalabad 2014 - 2018

INTERMEDIATE IN COMPUTER SCIENCES

Superior College, Faisalabad | 2012 - 2014

CONTACTS

Email: hassamsaleem55@gmail.com

Phone:+923070117297

Address: Faisalabad, Punjab Pakistan

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Web Development via PHP (Codelgniter) & ASP .NET with JQuery AJAX
- Desktop App Development via C# .Net
- SQL with Joins & Transactions in C#
- HTML/CSS/Bootstrap
- Project Management
- Software Knowledge
 - Visual Studio
 - Visual Code
 - o Sublime
 - NetBeans
 - o SQL Server
 - o Xampp
 - Microsoft Office(Word, Power Point, Excel)

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Reliable and professional
- Organized
- Time management
- Team player
- Fast Learner
- Motivated
- Good Internet Surfer